But when we go out to bed, it depends on what's going on in the world.
It could be quite a bit higher or maybe lower at the time.
So, by the event contract C-23-0E-B,
saw the waste transmission fee with Stella and Bartnell services
for the third and final extension.
Okay, with still on the transportation, the CPI came in at 4.4%.
They wanted a 3% increase.
If they deliver to Prairie View, it's $27.82.
If they go to Oak Grove, they have down $25.97.
It's a 3% increase.
And it's very similar.
It's exactly like we approved last year, a 3% increase.
Yes, so how much money is that?
Like I'd like to know, obviously we can all do math,
but there's nothing here to math.
Yeah, no matter how expensive it is, yeah, an air packet.
That's not a hydrogen sheet.
So I think we're all going to have the same questions as we did last year.
Yeah, how much more is this costing?
That's really what we're concerned about.
Obviously, for me a lot.
That's how we figured it was off of that.
I just think we're off a little better if we knew what those were.
We can get those number for you.
But when they're presented to us in this form.
You bet in this form, I'd like to know what I'm going to do.
Yes.
It's going to be around 80.
the sense is the increase per ton for.
For anyone's attention, you and no the over.
You know the over on.
Yeah.
OK.
5 all that makes no sense to be until I understand the end totally in fact on what else.
What is the dollar for you to work?
That will be easy.
Thank you.
Second.
2, 2, 3, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 5.
5 up.
But we're a bit of 25 dash 84 or 5 recruitment project to power and tail.
For components, 1, 2 and 5, which is included in their bid packet in their bid pack, not to
exceed 97,830 dollars a 10 cents, authorized the trust manager to execute the contract, contingent
upon legal review and funding availability.
So.
Go ahead.
On this one, we're only avoiding components, 1, 2 and 5, which is mostly fiber wire, different
types, the bits, the parts that will hook everything up and all.
That's mainly what's in 1, 2 and 5.
We had three bidders come in, you lit and packered, that's how their bid is on the paperwork that
came in.
But they're actually in partnership with power and tail.
So power and tail came in with 97,832 10 for this.
The next bidder, tech line did not bid the right bid, they put, they did, I think, the
equipment is what they did.
So they, they're not even a viable candidate and then K-Lix had a late bid so we couldn't accept
it.
If it's 10 seconds off of being able to receive it, you can't take it out of your state statutes.
So anyway, we want to go with power and tail for the 97,832 10.
So there's, there's three other components of this that were, that power and tail did not bid
on.
One of them is a virtual machine where, and we already, they did bid on that component, these other
components they didn't bid on them.
That component, we already use some of that, and we're getting pricing for that components
how we plan on satisfying that component.
There's another one that is on state bid that we're getting numbers off of that and then
there'll be another component that is that we'll have to put back out to bid because we didn't
have any bid on that.
One that's on state bid is some storage devices and I guess that's some of that's getting
hard to get, so it'd be interesting to see how that comes in.
Do you have the numbers on those components?
But these are all the stuff that's going to go in the knock in the head end.
That's what this stuff is going for this equipment part.
Is it all in the number of line-ups?
Tell the number of line items?
There are six components.
There are six components to it.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Did the one that bid the tech line, did they bid it on all six?
They didn't bid, they sent in the wrong bid.
They sent it to the wrong RFP because we bid out three things at that time.
They actually sent in the materials that you guys approved before.
They actually sent it into this one.
I would say that was quite a bit larger.
Yes.
That's why we didn't tell you this.
It was like a million plus.
That's like it.
Six other new business.
If any of which is written since the posting of this agenda, seven staff reports.
I thought things were going to be good to see that.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, Trustee, community announcements.
The government theater has some political events going on.
Good morning.
It's going to be here.
I think this next weekend.
This weekend.
So get your tickets.
It's a Christian and comedian.
I'll go around to that.
Yeah, I have to come in.
No, I'm trust management and education.
We closed on our level and that we approved the last week,
the next Wednesday.
So we can start contacts on our fiber stuff and starting
and then we're excited about that.
But from a call, I want to reach this board of two minutes
forward on a meter purchase.
So we'll start by in meters here as we find lots of contacts.
So that'll be good.
This has looked like as far as it's hung on for two years.
The meters, I mean, I think they come in 45,
they said 45 days, but I'm going to say 60 to 75.
And then we'll go out for,
we'll, during that rock time, we'll go out for a bit
for so many of them to be installed.
The water meters by private contractor.
We'll try to do something else, but it's just a lot.
And we'll start rolling on it.
Obviously, we're going to do a lot of public education.
Because, I mean, there may be meters or 50, 60, 70 years old out there,
you know, that I mean, I want you to get a brand new meter versus a 70 year old
meter.
It's going to read a lot more accurate.
So just to make people aware, like, hey, like,
because it's coming.
The English is parallel to that.
10, this means we're not being continued from council chambers,
we can be in the staff room for the purpose of the executive session.
I think a place in the regular meeting of the MIMA, M-I-P-F-A.